freelogovector.com 2011-11-02

# Privacy Policy » Free Logo Vector Graphics download and share

## Vector category

## Today term

## Privacy Policy

By using this site and downloading the vector, you acknowledged have read and agreed to both our disclaimer and privacy policy. We reserve the right to amend these terms from time to time. 

**Disclaimer** This disclaimer is a legal agreement between you and freelogovector. By downloading any material from our site or using them you agree that you have read and understood that the font copyrights belongs to the designer of such product. In cases, where there are no visible copyright notices, you need to assume that the file is copyrighted. Any use of the vector downloads is at your sole responsibility. We do not take any responsibility and we are not liable for any damage caused through use of these products, be it indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages (including but not limited to damages for loss of business, loss of profits, interruption or the like). To the best of our knowledge, all vector available on this site are free for redistribution. Should you encounter a vector that is not, please email us so that it can be immediately removed.

 **Privacy Policy** Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

On some pages, you may enter your email adress (to contact us). We use the email you provide for mailing service. We never use or share the email adress provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to us will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to contact as at hi[at]freelogovector.com. 

freelogovector.com have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at hi[at]freelogovector.com. 

## Logo Search 

## Sponsor

## Advertising

freelogovector.com is an online gallery of free logo vector graphics, brand logo, company logo, corporate logo. All the images on this site are free for personal use and a lot of them for commercial use, if you use any of the free logo vector art it would be nice if you could provide a link back to the authors web site. (But not always a requirement .) If you have any feature requests please let us know via the contact us page. We like feedback :-D

## Lates Download
